<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ktsamis</title><link>https://ktsamis.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on ktsamis</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 16:53:40 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ktsamis.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Understanding DevOps and GitOps: The Future of Software Development and Operations</title><link>https://ktsamis.github.io/posts/devops_gitops/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 16:53:40 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ktsamis.github.io/posts/devops_gitops/</guid><description>DevOps and GitOps are two important concepts in the field of software development and operations that are rapidly gaining popularity among organizations. They aim to bridge the gap between development and operations by bringing together the processes and tools used by both teams. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore what DevOps and GitOps are, how they work, and how you can use them in your everyday tasks.
What is DevOps?</description></item><item><title>Unleashing the Power of AI with ChatGPT: How to Use it Productively</title><link>https://ktsamis.github.io/posts/chatgpt/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 17:53:09 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ktsamis.github.io/posts/chatgpt/</guid><description>Artificial Intelligence (AI) has the potential to revolutionize many industries, from healthcare and finance to customer service and beyond. One of the most exciting AI technologies on the horizon is language models like ChatGPT, which have been developed by OpenAI.
ChatGPT is a cutting-edge AI model that uses deep learning to generate human-like responses to text input. It has been trained on a massive dataset of web pages, books, and other text sources, allowing it to understand and generate text on a wide range of topics.</description></item><item><title>Open source and Linux: Powering the Future of Technology</title><link>https://ktsamis.github.io/posts/linux/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 17:48:54 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ktsamis.github.io/posts/linux/</guid><description>Linux and open source are two integral components of the modern technology landscape. Open source refers to a development model where the source code of a piece of software is made freely available to the public. Linux, on the other hand, is an open-source operating system that was first released in 1991 by Linus Torvalds.
Since then, Linux has become one of the most widely used operating systems in the world, powering everything from supercomputers and data centers to smartphones and embedded systems.</description></item></channel></rss>